serpanalytics.com 2009-12-16

# Privacy Policy — SERP Analytics Help

**About**

**Our Audience**

**Help Home**

**Quick Start**

**Browser Configuration**

**Videos**

**About Forum**

**SERP Window**  
   General  
   SERP Windows  
   SEO Parameters  
   Dynamics & Graphs

**User Account**  
   General  
   Highlights  
   My Sites  
   Database Search

**SEO Tools**  
   Google Datacenter Tool

   Top 10,000 Keywords Tool

**Membership Plans**

Terms of Use  
Privacy Policy

| 

We will fully respect your personal privacy will be sure to keep all personal information private and will not share with any third party or any client unless we have written permission.

## Use of Cookies

SERPAnalytics will always turn your cookies on when you first come to our site. Because of the use of cookies, we will be able to identify you using your cookies, this way we can always improve our site in order to give better service. Cookies are also used to store all of your personal preferences and track what you search for and the trends of our customers. Cookies will not be shared with any third part unless able to show a court order, subpoena, or a search warrant. If you choose to disable your cookies, you might not have a great experience.

## Collected Information

In order to improve our level of service when you come to visit our site, we will save your browser language, IP address as well as browser type and time of day for each query. For instance, if you change your browser language, we might use that in order to display advertisements or search results that are in your chosen language.

## External Links

Any content that is displayed by the sites that link to our website is not approved nor looked at by our company therefore, Serpantalytics has no control over any of the content shown. These external sites can use their own cookies, or they can obtain any personal information or data. Our search results will use a URL re-director. This means that anything that comes from a clicked URL will be sent directly to our company and from there we can show you the right site that you need. This process helps us to improve the amount of service technology we have.

## Shared Information

None of the information that you share with our company will be shared with any other third party. These third parties include sponsors, business partners, or advertisers. The only information that will be shared is such that is non identifiable information. This can include the amount of visits you have at our site, or the most popular words you use to search for information. Any personal data will NOT be shared without getting your consent or unless you are ordered by law. This applies to any situations involving a court order, subpoena, search warrant or statute.

## Policy Changes

When you come to our site and you use our site, you need to know that you agree to the use of the collection of your information as explained above. We will always reserve the right to change this policy at any given time. Any changes will be posted on our website so that you will always be aware of the type of information that we are collecting and how we are using and disclosing it.
